保佑我，神父，我有罪。
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
你好吗?
How are you doing?
距离我上次忏悔已经两周了。
It's been two weeks since my last confession.
那段时间我做了很多坏事。
I've done a lot of bad things in that time.
我不去教堂，我多次徒然地使用上帝的名字，我骂我婆婆，但那是用意大利语说的，所以她听不懂，所以我不知道这算不算。
Didn't go to church, I took the Lord's name in vain quite a few times, I cursed my mother-in-law, but it was in Italian, so she couldn't understand, so I don't know if that counts.
这也算
It counts.
好吧……我背叛了我的妻子。
Okay... And I cheated on my wife.
你犯奸淫了吗?
You committed adultery?
是的。
Yes.
多少次?
How many times?
在过去两周内已经打了五次了。
Five times the last two weeks.
等待……不,那是错的。
Wait... No, that's wrong.
这星期来了四次……与三个女人…上周有三次…和另外两个女人。
It was four times this week... with three women... and three times last week... with two other women.
哇。
Wow.
另外，这周的一个女人和上周一样…或者有两个女人是一样的，所以我想这就…什么?我不知道。七次。
Plus, one of the women from this week was the same as last week... or maybe two of the women was the same, so I guess that makes... What? I don't know. Seven times.
我是说，不止七次了，神父。
I mean, it was more than seven times, Father.
大概有10到12次，但是，你知道，就像……在7个不同的场合，只有5个不同的女人，但有些女人不止一次……有些人还会来好几次。
It was more like 10 or 12 times, but, you know, it was like... on seven different occasions, only with five different women, but some of the women more than once... Some of them quite a few times.
事实上，这很难说，神父。
In fact, it's hard to say, Father.
我没有仔细数过，但过去两周有十几次…多少有出入。
I didn't exactly keep count, but let's say a dozen times in the last two weeks... give or take a few times.
罗莎莉!
Rosalie!
乔伊，我还在等肉丸呢，宝贝。
Joey, I'm still waiting for those meatballs, baby.
我马上就来。
I'll be right with you.
谢谢你过来。
Hey, thanks for stopping by.
罗莎莉，温德尔要再来一杯啤酒。
Rosalie, Wendel wants another beer.
原谅我。
Excuse me.
本尼!你在这里做什么?我以为你去度假了。
Benny!What are you doing here? I thought you was on vacation.
昨天回来。
Got back yesterday.
玛莎怎么样?她是很棒的。
How's Martha? She's terrific.
帮我转达乔伊的问候。
You tell her Joey said hello.
我会的。
I will.
德沃，肉丸，肉丸。来吧。
Devo, the meatball, the meatballs. Come on.
我一分钟后就来，伙计们。
I'll be with you in one minute, folks.
唐娜·乔伊，你穿迷你裙真好看。
Donna Joy, you're looking mighty nice in that mini.
谢谢,乔伊。
Thanks, Joey.
你自己看起来也不错。
You're looking pretty good yourself.
是的,你觉得呢?谢谢。
Yeah, you think? Thanks.
乔伊的披萨。
Joey's Pizza.
嘿，泰，你好吗?
Hey, Ty, how you doing?
你想要辣香肠，你有辣香肠。
How many You want pepperoni, you got pepperoni.
德沃，把这个拿出来。
Devo, take this out.
罗莎莉!
Rosalie!
图斯基要来拿六个派
Tulsky's coming by to pick up six pies.
我们需要更多的意大利辣香肠。在后面。
We need more pepperoni. It's in the back.
乔伊的披萨。
Joey's Pizza.
嘿，宝贝，你好吗?
Hey, baby, how you doing?
哦!
Oh!
不，不，现在很糟糕。
No, no, now's bad.
现在是不好的。
Now's bad.
很忙。
Very busy.
以后怎么样?
How about later on?
稍后。好吗?
Later on. Okay?
我得挂电话了。我妻子的到来。
I've got to hang up. My wife's coming.
好吧,再见。
Okay, bye.
谢谢你打来电话。
Thanks for calling.
安静点，好吗?
Be quiet, will you?
闭嘴!
Shut up!
嗨,妈妈。嗨,妈妈。
Hi, Mom. Hi, Mom.
多米尼克。
Dominic.
Devo。
Devo.
“克里斯托尔先生，让它发光吧。
"Mr. Crystal, let it shine.
像豪猪一样的尖刺。”
Spikes just like a porcupine."
你好,你们两个。
Hello, you two.
这就跟你问声好！
Hi!
这是热的。我马上就来。
This is hot. I'll be with you in a minute.
我要把这个给你。
I'm going to drop this off.
好的。我要去看爸爸。
Okay. I'm going to go see Dad.
嗨,爸爸。
Hi, Daddy.
谁说的?
Who said that?
什么
What
让我看看你的照片，多姆。
Let me see your picture, Dom.
哦，那真是太好了。它是什么?
Oh, that's really good. What is it?
它看起来像什么?
What does it look like?
看起来像披萨饼?
It looks like a pizza pie?
妈妈，这是一朵花。
Mom, it's a flower.
哦,我很抱歉。
Oh, I'm sorry.
你觉得呢?
What do you think?
米开朗基罗。
Michelangelo.
看看这个。
Look at that.
噢，正义的捍卫者。你好。
Oh, the defenders of justice. Hello.
哦。滚开，警察们!
Uh-oh. Cheese it, the cops!
给你，拉里。所有的设置。
Here you go, Larry. All set.
香肠和“房间”，重“房间”。
Sausage and 'rooms, heavy on the 'rooms.
谢谢你,乔伊。
Thank you, Joey.
卡洛斯，怎么了?
Carlos, what's the matter?
什么都没有。
Nothing.
嘿，孩子们，你们好吗?
Hey, kids, how's it going?
好的。
Okay.
拉里,拉里,拉里。
Larry, Larry, Larry.
看看多米尼克今天干的好事
Look what Dominic did today.
你见过这么美的东西吗?
You ever see anything so beautiful?
多米尼克,可爱。那是什么，一朵花吗?
Dominic, that's lovely. What is that, a flower?
不，是披萨。
No, it's a pizza.
我猜是意大利辣香肠。
It's pepperoni, I bet.
是的，有可能。我不确定。是的。
Yeah, it could be. I'm not sure. Yeah.
我爱意大利辣香肠。
I love pepperoni.
下一个时间。
Next time.
你总是说下次。
You always say next time.
我听说你抓住了那个抢劫7- 11便利店的家伙。
I heard you caught that guy who was robbing all them 7-Elevens.
你抓住那家伙了?
You caught that guy?
正确的。
Right.
昨晚把他接走了。
Picked him up last night.
感谢上帝!
Thank God!
你做得很好。
You're doing a great job.
你听到了吗?
You hear that?
这就是为什么在美国，我们生活安全，生活美好，因为我们有拉里·斯库纳(Larry Schooner)和卡洛斯·威利(Carlos Wiley)这样的警察，他们确保每个人都做自己该做的事。
That's how come, in America, we live safe, have a good life, because we've got cops like Larry Schooner and Carlos Wiley who make sure everybody does what he's supposed to do.
你努力工作，纳税，遵守法律，你可以得到你想要的任何东西。
You work hard, pay taxes, obey the law, you can have anything you want.
我想让我的孩子们明白我们的国家是多么伟大。
I want my kids to understand what a great country we've got here.
我想他们能理解。
I think they understand.
罗莎莉，盯着店里。
Hey, Rosalie, keep your eye on the shop.
我得去看看莱西·弗林的水管。
I've got to look at Lacey Flynn's plumbing.
好吧,亲爱的。
Okay, sweetie.
她的管道吗?
Her plumbing?
德沃，你那边完事后，我要你到后面去清理一下垃圾桶。
Devo, when you're done there, I want you to go around back and clean out the garbage cans.
它们满是蛆虫。
They're full of maggots.
蛆虫。这是完美的。我爱那个男人。
Maggots. That's perfect. I love that man.
别担心。我和你一起做。
Don't worry. I'll do it with you.
不，拜托，那是我的工作，照顾蛆虫。
No, please, that's my job, taking care of maggots.
你过得如何?
How you doing?
这是这周他第三次去看莱西的管道了。
This is the third time this week he's gone up there to visit Lacey's pipes.
拜托，他是这栋楼的主人。
Come on, he owns the building.
他得处理好这件事。
He has to take care of it.
看到她看他的眼神了吗?
See the way she looks at him?
这不是他的错。
That's not his fault.
除此之外,她是孤独的。我为她感到难过。
Besides, she's lonely. I feel sorry for her.
不要为她感到难过。
Don't feel sorry for her.
这对乔伊来说太方便了。
It's too convenient for Joey.
嘿，你不应该那样说话。
Hey, you shouldn't talk like that.
它是不正确的。
It's not right.
乔伊是我的丈夫。
Joey's my husband.
我不想看到你受伤。
I don't want to see you get hurt.
我能照顾好自己。别担心我。
I can take care of myself. Don't worry about me.
是谁?
Who is it?
是送披萨的。
It's the pizza man.
你好,披萨的人。
Hello, pizza man.
你好。
Hello.
我来检查你的管道。
I'm here to check your pipes.
我真高兴，水喷得到处都是。
I'm so glad because water's squirting everywhere.
觉得她漂亮吗?
Think she's pretty?
是的，我想是的。
Yeah, I guess so.
我有眼睛，你知道吗?
I've got eyes, you know?
我知道很多女孩都为乔伊疯狂，而且他对女人也很有眼光。
I can see a lot of girls are crazy for Joey, and he has an eye for the ladies too.
没关系。他是意大利人。他可以看。
That's okay. He's Italian. He's allowed to look.
在现实中，我们知道，有些男人做的不仅仅是看。
In reality as we know it, some men do more than look.
你不相信任何人，德沃。这就是你的全部麻烦。
You don't trust anyone, Devo. That's your whole trouble.
我相信你。
I trust you.
乔伊绝不会背叛我的。
Joey would never run around on me.
罗莎莉——他永远不会。
Rosalie-- He never would.
让我这么说吧。
Let me put it this way.
假设你做了一个他做的梦，而这个梦被证明是真的。
Let's say you had a dream that he did, and the dream turned out to be true.
你会怎么做?
What would you do?
我会自杀的，如果我感觉不好，我会杀了他。
I'd kill myself, and if I didn't feel any better, I'd kill him.
是的。
Yeah.
乔伊，再待一会儿。
Joey, stay a little longer.
哦,我不能。我有很多工作要做。
Oh, I can't. I've got a lot of work.
也许你过会儿再来?
Maybe you'll come back later?
可能过几天吧。
Maybe later.
也许在这里过夜?
Maybe even spend the night?
你疯了吗?
What are you, crazy?
我不能在这儿过夜。
I can't spend the night.
我有妻子和家庭。
I've got a wife and family.
乔伊，你不爱你的妻子。
Joey, you don't love your wife.
谁说?
Who says so?
我当然爱她。
Of course I love her.
我跟你做爱不代表我不爱她。
Just because I make love to you doesn't mean I don't love her.
那是什么样的婚姻?
What kind of marriage is that?
这是一段美好的婚姻。
It's a good marriage.
我买菜，她做饭。
I buy the food, she cooks it.
我可以为你做饭。
I can cook for you.
你不能给我做饭。你不是我妻子。
You can't cook for me. You're not my wife.
你甚至都不是意大利人。
You're not even Italian.
你妻子也不是。
Neither is your wife.
她是欧亚混血什么的。
She's some kind of Eurasian or something.
不，她不是那里的人。
No, she's not from there.
她她妈妈是南斯拉夫人
She's-- Her mother's from Yugoslavia.
这是一个天主教国家。就在意大利旁边。
It's a good Catholic country. Right next to Italy.
事实上，它曾经是意大利的一部分。
In fact, it used to be part of Italy.
我认为。
I think.
乔伊，这里不是意大利。这里是美国。
Joey, this isn't Italy. This is America.
嘿，美洲是一个意大利人发现的，它是以另一个意大利人的名字命名的。
Hey, America was discovered by one Italian, and it's named after another.
那又怎样?那能证明什么呢?
So what? What does that prove?
这证明美国是一个意大利国家。
It proves that America is an Italian country.
我得走了。
I've got to go.
乔伊，如果你是个虔诚的天主教徒，为什么还要通奸?
Joey, if you're such a good Catholic, why do you commit adultery?
我一个人。
I'm a man.
我体内有很多荷尔蒙。
I've got a lot of hormones in my body.
他跳得那么高，高，高*
* He jumped So high, high, high *
*他击中天空，天空，天空*没有回来，回来，回来*
* He hit the sky, sky, sky * And didn't come Back, back, back *
*直到7月4日*
* Till The Fourth of July-ly-ly *
好了，又来了。
Okay, here we go again.
最后一次。一个,两个,三个。
Last time. One, two, three.
*玛丽小姐，麦克，麦克，麦克*穿着黑色，黑色，黑色*
* Miss Mary Mac, Mac, Mac * All dressed In black, black, black *
*配有银色纽扣，纽扣，纽扣*
* With silver Buttons, buttons, buttons *
她的背，背，背*
* All down Her back, back, back *
她问她的妈妈，妈妈，妈妈
* She asked Her mother, mother, mother *
为50美分，美分，美分*看大象大象，大象*
* For 50 cents, cents, cents * To watch the elephants Elephants, elephants *
*跳过栅栏，栅栏，栅栏*
* Jump over The fence, fence, fence *
他们跳得那么高，高，高*
* They jumped So high, high, high *
*他们击中天空，天空，天空*没有回来，回来，回来*
* They hit the sky, sky, sky * And didn't come Back, back, back *
*直到7月4日*
* Till The Fourth of July-ly-ly *
然后他们开始担心，担心，担心
* Then they got Worried, worried, worried *
*去了香港，香港，香港*
* And went To Hong Kong, Kong, Kong *
*去看《金刚，金刚，金刚》*
* To see The King Kong, Kong, Kong *
为了得到他的建议，邪恶，邪恶
* To get His advice, vice, vice *
但是他没有，没有，没有
* But he didn't have Any, any, any *
所以他们回家，回家，回家*
* So they went Back home, home, home *
他们没有得到任何建议——这是一种恶习
* They didn't get any Advice-vice-vice *
所以他们去了罗马，罗马，罗马
* So they went To Rome, Rome, Rome *
*没有回家，回家，回家…＊
* And didn't come Home, home, home... *
罗莎莉，听我说。
Rosalie, listen to this.
这上面说有个女人被自己家的植物活活吃掉了。
It says here some woman was eaten alive by her own houseplants.
你能想象吗?
Can you imagine?
妈妈，还要咖啡吗?
Mama, want more coffee?
如果没有，我就把它扔了。
If not, I'm going to throw it out.
哦,不。去做吧。把它扔出去。
Oh, no. Go ahead. Throw it out.
否则我整晚都得在厕所里。
Otherwise, I'll be in the bathroom all night.
还记得你父亲每晚睡前都要喝一大杯黑咖啡吗?
Remember how your father used to drink a big cup of black coffee every night right before bed?
是的，也很热。
Yeah, boiling hot too.
有四个糖。
With four sugars.
非常甜的。
Very sweet.
就像他。
Just like him.
你知道的…我每天都想他。
You know... I miss him every day.
我几乎忘记了我讨厌他的一切。
I forget almost everything I hate about him.
是的,我知道。
Yeah, I know.
我也想他。
I miss him too.
我得到了它。
I got it.
他跳得那么高，高，高，他撞到了天空，天空，天空*
* He jumped so high, high, high He hit the sky, sky, sky *
嘿,Devo。
Hey, Devo.
你好。
Hello.
进来吧。你过得如何?
Come on in. How you doing?
我做的很好。
I'm doing good.
我正准备看完球赛呢。
I was just going to catch the end of the ball game.
想看吗?
Want to watch?
不用了，谢谢。
Oh, no, thank you.
我想我会去拜访罗莎莉和娜佳妈妈。
I think I'll visit with Rosalie and Mama Nadja.
确定。
Sure.
他们在厨房里。
They're in the kitchen.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我该怎么办?
What do I do?
你从袋子里拿出一个符文。
You reach in the bag and take out a rune.
任何一个吗?
Any one?
它们都很漂亮，你等着瞧吧。
Well, they're all beautiful, you'll see.
它们是什么，符文吗?
What are they, runes?
它们是石头，非常有灵性
They're stones. They're very spiritual.
他们有超自然的力量。
They have metaphysical powers.
他们做了什么?
And what do they do?
它不会说，他们会告诉你你在哪里。
It wouldn't say-- Well, they tell you where you're at.
我在家里。
I'm at home.
我们在这里。
We're right here.
你在说什么?
What are you saying?
不,在精神上。
No, spiritually.
在精神上，它们告诉你你在哪里。
Spiritually, they tell you where you're at.
我不知道该不该这么做。
I don't know if I should do this.
我是说，我是天主教徒。
I mean, I'm a Catholic.
他们并不反对上帝或其他什么。
They're not against God or anything.
去做吧。试一试。有什么坏处呢?
Go ahead. Try it. What can it hurt?
好的。
Okay.
哦，这个不错。我喜欢这个。
Oh, this is a good one. I love this one.
这是力量。
This is strength.
力量?
Strength?
是的。
Yes.
快攻!快攻!
Fast break! Fast break!
看上去不错。
Looking good.
是的!是的!
Yes! Yes!
*……意思是不要忘记你是我的爱人
* ...means don't forget You are my darling *
"更替和更新的符文，"暗示是时候改变你现在的生活了"
"The rune of replacement and renewal, "suggesting that the time has come to change the life you're living."
它没有这么说。让我看看。
It doesn't say that. Let me see.
确定它。看。
Sure it does. Look.
你以为我瞎编的吗?
Think I made that up?
不，但我了解你。
No, but I know you.
我知道你在想什么。
I know what you think.
罗莎莉，给我拿瓶啤酒，好吗?
Rosalie, bring me a beer, will you?
我觉得你应该让他自己去买啤酒。
I think you should let him get his own beer.
我不介意。他努力工作。我喜欢照顾他。
I don't mind. He works hard. I like taking care of him.
有一件事叫做妇女解放。
There's such a thing as women's liberation.
她不需要做奴隶。
She doesn't have to be a slave.
这是正确的。
That's right.
上周在电视上，我听说有个女人捅了她丈夫27刀。
Last week on TV, I heard about a woman who stabbed her husband 27 times.
你知道为什么吗?因为他拒绝把芥末罐的盖子放回去。
You know why? Because he refused to put the top back on the mustard jar.
是的,27倍。
Yeah, 27 times.
你能想象吗?
Can you imagine?
有花生或椒盐卷饼之类的东西可以嚼吗?
We got any peanuts or pretzels, something to munch on?
不，我想我们完了。
No, I think we're out.
我们总是出去。
We're always out.
在我妈妈家，总是有很多食物可以吃。
My mama's house, there's always plenty food to eat.
也许你该和你妈妈一起住。
Maybe you should live with your mama.
不要讽刺。
Don't be sarcastic.
别逼我。
Don't be a nudge.
别叫我助推器。
Don't call me that nudge thing.
来吧。我是意大利人。我喜欢吃。
Come on. I'm Italian. I like to eat.
我是南斯拉夫人。
I'm Yugoslavian.
我不喜欢做饭，尤其不喜欢做嫩鸡。
I don't like to cook, especially for nudges.
是啊，别叫我傻逼。
Yeah, don't call me a nudge.
轻推,推,推。
Nudge, nudge, nudge.
把那双鞋给我。
Give me those shoes.
你今晚又要出去吗?
You going out again tonight?
嘿，罗莎莉，快点。
Hey, Rosalie, come on.
什么?我什么也没说。
What? I haven't said anything.
我每天都工作。一整天。好吧?每一天。
I work every day. All day. Okay? Every day.
晚上，我喜欢放松，出去玩，你知道的。
At night, I like to relax, go out, have fun, you know.
我以为你待在家里。
I thought you were staying home.
对什么?
What for?
我不知道。
I don't know.
谁知道呢?
Who knows?
嗯,像什么?
Well, like what?
首先，我们有文书工作。
Well, for one thing, we've got paperwork.
文书工作吗?
Paperwork?
每月的账单，保险，抵押贷款，电话费。
The monthly bills, the insurance, the mortgage, the phone bill.
我要出去。
I'm going out.
*玛丽·麦克小姐，麦克，麦克*在迪斯科舞厅Theque, Theque *
* Miss Mary Mac, Mac, Mac * At the discotheque Theque, theque *
*我要抓住她，她，她*在她的背上，背上，背上……＊
* I'm going to get her, her, her * Down on Her back, back, back... *
请伏特加。
Vodka, please.
米奇，这都怪我。
Mickey, that's on me.
没问题，乔伊。
You got it, Joey.
我叫乔伊·博卡。
Joey Boca's my name.
你知道吗?
And you know what?
我知道你的一些事。
I know something about you.
是吗?你对我了解多少?
Yeah? What do you know about me?
我知道你以前从没来过这里。
I know you never been in here before in your life.
真的可能是吧。
Really Maybe I have.
如果你说了，我早就知道了。
If you had, I would have known about it.
人们会谈论它。
People would have talked about it.
比如"乔伊，你看"那天晚上这里面是什么?
Like, "Joey, you see "what was in here the other night?
天哪，真是个美人。”
My God, what a beauty."
这是真的。
It's true.
不，像你这样的人不常来。
No, someone like you doesn't come around that often.
这就像一个全国性的节日。
It's like a national holiday.
明白我的意思吗?
Know what I mean?
你不会忘记的。
You don't forget it.
谢谢你请我喝酒，但我有伴了。
Listen, I appreciate the drink, but I'm with someone.
非常幸运的人。
Someone very lucky.
我希望我也能那么幸运。
I wish I could be that lucky.
我看着你，对自己说，天哪，能和这个女人走在一起的男人一定觉得自己是人间之王
I look at you and I say to myself, "My God, the man who gets to walk "with this woman must feel like a king on earth."
这是给你。
Here's to you.
我想我最好回去了。
I guess I'd better get back.
让我看看你的男朋友。
Show me your boyfriend.
我想亲眼看看他，这样我的余生就能希望我是他了。
I want to see him with my own eyes, so I can spend the rest of my life wishing I was him.
他坐在角落里。
He's sitting in the corner.
在那里。
Over there.
不是穿黄色衬衫的那个吗?
Not the one in the yellow shirt?
是的,就是他。
Yeah, that's him.
不。
No.
是的。
Yeah.
不。
No.
是的,就是他。
Yeah, that's him.
为什么?
Why?
你指望我相信像你这样的美女，一个任何男人都愿意和她在一起的女人，会和这样的人在一起吗?
You expect me to believe that a beauty like you, a woman any man would die to be with, is throwing herself away on someone like that?
你可以拥有任何人。任何人。
You could have anyone. Anyone.
你为什么要带走他?
Why would you take him?
他不是我男朋友什么的。
He's not my boyfriend or anything.
我只是和他一起来的。
I just came here with him.
我并没有爱上他什么的。
I'm not in love with him or anything.
当然不是。你怎么可能?
Of course not. How could you be?
他到底要不要看?
Is he going to watch or what?
你觉得困扰吗?
Does it bother you?
我是意大利人，你知道的。
Well, I'm Italian, you know.
我不能和一个有德国牧羊犬的女人做爱。
I can't make love to a woman with a German shepherd in the room.
这对他来说很尴尬。
It's awkward for him.
你不能吗?
You can't?
原谅我。
Excuse me.
给你。
Here you go.
好啊!。
Attaboy.
再会,亨氏。
Auf Wiedersehen, Heinz.
我想不出来。
I can't figure it out.
像你这样年轻英俊的小伙子，怎么老是和罗莎莉在一起?
A young, good-looking guy like you, how come you're always hanging out with Rosalie?
我喜欢她的陪伴。
I enjoy her company.
你不是要和我妻子同居吧?
You're not moving in on my wife?
不，当然不是。你在开玩笑吧?
No, of course not. What are you, kidding?
这是可笑的。
That's ludicrous.
你是荒谬的。
You're being ridiculous.
可笑的是什么?
What's ridiculous?
没有人能比得上罗莎莉。
There's nobody like Rosalie.
正确的。
Right.
她是最好的。
She's the best.
完全正确。
Exactly.
我不敢相信你会这么说。
I can't believe you're saying that.
为什么不呢?她是我的妻子。
Why not? She's my wife.
是的,我知道。我看着别的女人。
Yeah, I know. I look at other women.
好的。那又怎样?这很自然。
Okay. So what? That's only natural.
我是一个人。
I'm a human man.
这不会伤害罗莎莉。
It don't hurt Rosalie.
你怎么能这么说?
How can you say that?
就算她知道，她也不在乎。
Even if she knows, she don't care.
她就是这样的人。
That's how she is.
哦,是吗?
Oh yeah?
这是纯粹的投影。
Well, that's pure projection.
纯粹的什么?
Pure what?
投影。
Projection.
这是投影，你想怎么想。
It's projection, what you want to think.
我想怎么想?
What I want to think?
是啊，一想到她开心你就觉得很开心。
Yeah, it makes you feel good to think that she's happy.
是啊!
Yeah!
只要她开心，我就开心。
As long as she's happy, I'm happy.
我很高兴我们能相互理解。
I'm glad we understand each other.
嗯,我也是。
Well, me too.
我听说斯宾诺去贝灵汉了?
I hear Spino took off to Bellingham?
是的。
Yeah.
是吗?
Yeah?
我得走了，伙计。
Got to go, man.
好了，别紧张，比利。
Okay, take it easy, Billy.
你怎么认识这些怪人的?
How do you know these weird people?
那家伙和我哥哥一起在监狱里。
That guy was in prison with my brother.
我第一个男朋友有一辆哈雷摩托。
My first boyfriend had a Harley.
罗科·雅各布斯。
Rocco Jacobs.
他真是个了不起的人。
What a piece of work he was.
我们过去走得很快。
We used to go fast.
也许我应该买辆自行车。
Maybe I should get a bike.
当然。为什么不呢?让女孩们发疯。
Sure. Why not? Drives the girls crazy.
那时候我很狂野。
I was wild back then.
那么Rocco怎么了?
So what happened to Rocco?
乔伊博卡发生。
Joey Boca happened.
他说:“嘿，我是乔伊。你想出去吗?
He said, "Hey, I'm Joey. You want to go out?
你和那个混蛋在一起做什么?”
What are you doing with that jerk?"
我一看到乔伊，就知道他就是我的真命天子。
As soon as I saw Joey, I knew he was the one.
这么快?
So fast?
当然,快。
Sure, fast.
我做我感觉的事。
I do what I feel.
那你一定想自杀。
Then you must have felt suicidal.
闭嘴。
Shut up.
总有一天，你会找到一个很棒的女人，你会用这辆大摩托车把她逼疯。
Some day, you're going to find a wonderful woman, and you'll drive her crazy with this big motorcycle.
我找到了一个很好的女人，但她已经结婚了。
I found myself a wonderful woman, but she's married.
德沃，你对我的自尊有好处。
Devo, you're good for my ego.
你得去认识和你年龄相仿的人。
You've got to meet somebody your own age.
为什么?
Why?
你的心不知道你的年龄。
Your heart doesn't know how old you are.
你好。乔伊在吗?
Hi. Is Joey around?
不,他不是。
No, he's not.
我是他的妻子。我能帮你吗?
I'm his wife. Can I help you?
哦……我在一个保龄球馆认识他的，他告诉我他有几套公寓要出租。
Oh... I met him at a bowling alley, and he told me he had some apartments to rent.
他现在就在上面。
He's up there right now.
修复管道。
Fixing the pipes.
这是我的朋友，德沃。
This is my friend, Devo.
你叫什么名字?
What is your name?
布丽姬特。
Bridget.
布丽姬特,Devo见面。
Bridget, meet Devo.
嗨。
Hi.
你好。
Hello.
来吧。我带你上去。
Come on. I'll take you up.
我想我是时候搬出我的房子了。
I think it's time I was moving out of my house.
我搬出去的时候和你差不多大。
I was about your age when I moved out.
我和乔伊结婚了。
I got married to Joey.
现在我妈妈和我们住在一起。
Now my mother lives with us.
那一定很有趣。
That must be fun.
没关系。
It's okay.
乔伊来了。
Oh, here's Joey now.
布丽奇特，你好吗?你在这里做什么?
Bridget, how you doing? What are you doing here?
她想看看其中一间公寓，宝贝。
She wants to look at one of the apartments, baby.
今天好吗?
Today?
你们有空房吗?
Do you have any vacancies?
我们下个月可能会有一个。
We might have one coming up next month.
趁她还在，不妨去看看。
Might as well take a look while she's here.
是的，是的。
Yeah, yeah.
不。
No.
不，现在不是时候。
No, it's-- It's not a good time.
可能明天吧。这是怎么回事?
Maybe tomorrow. How's that?
当然。明天。
Sure. Tomorrow.
很高兴见到你，博卡太太。
Well, it was nice to meet you, Mrs. Boca.
罗莎莉。
Rosalie.
再见。
Bye.
再见,现在。
Bye-bye, now.
再见。
Bye-bye.
她远道而来。
She came all this way.
你今天不能给她看吗?
You couldn't show her today?
不,不。我有很多事要做。我不是超人。
No, no. I've got a lot to do. I'm not Superman.
嘿,乔伊!
Hey, Joey!
你忘记了这一点。
You forgot this.
谢谢。
Thanks.
我不喜欢那个杜威·布朗。
I don't like that Dewey Brown.
为什么不呢?她是个好女孩。
Why not? She's a nice girl.
她看上你了，乔伊。
She's got eyes for you, Joey.
什么?
What?
我看得出来。
I can see that.
来吧。她只是个孩子。
Come on. She's only a kid.
她很漂亮。你觉得她漂亮吗?
She's very pretty. You think she's pretty?
她很漂亮。
She's pretty.
她的身材也很漂亮。
She's got a beautiful body too.
那又怎样?我在乎什么?
So what? What do I care?
你是世界上最好的妻子。
You're the best wife in the world.
我还想要什么?
What more could I want?
你工作太辛苦了。
You work too hard.
你应该找个水管工。
You should get a plumber.
我付不起，你知道的。
I can't afford that, and you know it.
我从来没让你在家修过东西。
I can never get you to fix anything at home.
你妈妈修理一切。
Your mother fixes everything.
half-woman half-wrench。
half-woman, half-wrench.
所以它在这里。看到了吗?
So this goes right here. See?
保存在一起。
Holds it together.
这是餐厅，不是车库。
This is a restaurant, not a garage.
娜佳奶奶什么都能修。
Grandma Nadja can fix anything.
她昨天修好了妈妈的车。
She fixed Mommy's car yesterday.
交流发电机被枪杀了。
Alternator was shot.
一个女人做这种工作是不正常的。
It's not natural, a woman doing this kind of work.
你知道，做这种工作的人每小时能赚20到30美元。
You know, people get paid $20, $30 an hour for this kind of work.
你可以免费食宿。你还想怎么样?
You get free room and board. What more do you want?
别那样跟妈妈说话!
Don't talk to Mama that way!
她属于老年之家。
She belongs in an old-age home.
她说了什么?
What did she say?
别听他的，好吗?
Don't listen to him, okay?
我待会儿再来。
I'll come back later.
怎么了，多姆?
What's the matter, Dom?
发生了什么事?
What happened?
我伤了手指。
I hurt my finger.
让我看看。
Let me see.
我们可以解决这个问题。
We can fix that.
这里。没有问题。
Here. No problem.
我们马上修好。
We'll fix it right up.
现在把它放进嘴里。
Now put that in your mouth.
这是怎么回事?
How's that?
更好的好。这是我的男孩。
Better Good. That's my boy.
我们可以吃吗?
Can we eat?
我返回。
I'm returning these.
好的。谢谢。
Okay. Thanks.
我在图书馆做什么?
What am I doing in a library?
那是什么香水吗?你闻起来真香。
What's that perfume? You smell so good.
乔伊。
Joey.
什么?
What?
不在这里。他们会把我们赶出去的。
Not here. They're going to throw us out.
好。
Good.
拿上你的书，我们走吧。
Get your book, and let's get out of here.
我们要去哪里?
Where are we going to go?
我们去你家，玩得开心点。
I say we go to your place, have a good time.
你妻子呢?
What about your wife?
不，她不能来。
No, she can't come.
都准备好了吗?来吧。
All set? Come on.
我很快就要回去工作了。
I've got to get back to work soon.
博卡夫人?
Mrs. Boca?
你好,米莉。嗨。
Hi, Millie. Hi.
你没事吧?
You okay?
有人抢劫你了吗?
Did somebody mug you?
我很好,亲爱的。
I'm fine, sweetie.
我…我丢了一些东西，但没关系。
I... I lost something, but it's okay.
你们去吧，伙计们。我会没事的。
You go ahead, guys. I'll be all right.
我们能帮你找找吗?
Could we help you look for it?
我会找到它。
I'll find it.
好的。
Okay.
来吧。
Come on.
傻瓜。愚蠢的傻瓜!
Fool. Stupid fool!
他离婚吗?不,从来没有。我为什么要呢?
Divorce him? No, never. Why should I?
好让他搬去和别的女人同居吗?
So he can move in with some other woman?
我宁愿他先死。
I'd rather see him dead first.
很好。他该死。
Good. He deserves to die.
把脏毛巾扔得到处都是。他是一个烂摊子。
Leaves dirty towels everywhere. He's a mess.
我恨他，妈妈。
I hate him, Mama.
这么多年来，我真是个傻瓜。
All these years, what a fool I am.
德沃也警告过我。
Devo tried to warn me too.
他死得越早，你就活得越早。
The sooner he's dead, the sooner you begin to live.
我认识一个需要钱的人。
I know someone who needs money.
他会这样做。
He'd do it.
他是个好孩子，人很好。
He's a good boy, very nice.
你是怎么认识这类人的?
How do you know these sort of people?
我有很多朋友。
I've got a lot of friends.
你知道的。
You know that.
杀手?
Killers?
不是真正的杀手，不是。
Not real killers, no.
他们这么做只是为了钱。
They only do it for money.
如果我们被抓了怎么办?
What if we get caught?
哦,请罗莎莉。
Oh, Rosalie, please.
在美国，人们互相残杀。
In America, people kill each other left and right.
这就像是全国性的消遣。
It's like national pastime.
没有人被抓。
Nobody gets caught.
我不知道。
I don't know.
我只是很久没做过这种事了。
I just haven't done this kind of thing in a long time.
好吧，它很容易回来。
Well, it comes back easy.
上次是什么时候?
When was last time?
那是很久以前的事了。我记不清楚了。
It was a long time ago. I don't remember exactly.
好吧，你会为我做的。
Well, you'll do it for me.
好的。
Okay.
为了纪念你和我祖母的友谊，我保证我会干掉他。
In honor of your friendship with my grandmother, I guarantee I'll take this guy out.
好的。你真是个好孩子。
Okay. You're very good boy.
现在有这么多年轻人，他们不尊重人。
So many young people today, they have no respect.
我认为这是因为电视，太多的性和暴力。
I think it's because of TV, so much sex and violence.
是啊，谁能想到这个世界会变成什么样子?
Yeah, who can figure what this world's coming to?
错误的房子。
Wrong house.
狗娘养的，混蛋!
Son of a bitch, bastard!
罗莎莉!
Rosalie!
这是难以置信的。就差这么多。
It was unbelievable. It was by this much.
进来吧。坐在这儿吧。
Come on in. Sit down here.
谢谢你这么快就过来。
I appreciate your coming over so quick.
好吧,没关系。
Well, it's okay.
听说过吗?
Ever hear of it?
想用棒球棍打我吗?
Trying to hit me with a baseball bat?
我的天，真是难以置信。
My God, it's unbelievable.
罗莎莉，你在干什么?
Rosalie, what are you doing?
给斯库纳警探倒杯咖啡。
Get Detective Schooner a cup of coffee.
不。我很好,罗莎莉。谢谢你！
No. I'm okay, Rosalie. Thank you.
不，她会在五分钟内给你煮咖啡。
No, she'll make you coffee in five minutes.
谢谢,乔伊。我正在努力戒掉它。
Thanks, Joey. I'm trying to give it up.
不，拜托，你不喝咖啡了?从没听说过。
No, come on, please-- You give up coffee? Never heard of that.
让我神经兮兮的。
Makes me jumpy.
神经兮兮的?
Jumpy?
罗莎莉，给拉里来点培根和鸡蛋怎么样?
Rosalie, how about some bacon and eggs for Larry?
他努力工作。
He works hard.
我什么都不要，谢谢。罗莎莉，请坐。
Nothing for me, thank you. Rosalie, please sit down.
我不是来吃早餐的，乔伊。
I didn't come here for breakfast, Joey.
好的。从一开始。
Okay. From the beginning.
当然，从一开始。好的。
Sure, from the beginning. Okay.
有个戴着亚伯拉罕·林肯面具的疯子想用棒球棍爆我的头。
Some maniac in an Abraham Lincoln mask tries to brain me with a baseball bat.
这就是整个故事。
That's the whole story.
你能看到他长什么样吗?
Yeah, could you see what he looked like?
是的，他看起来就像亚伯拉罕·林肯准备击球。
Yeah, he looked like Abraham Lincoln coming up to bat.
这算哪门子杀人方式?
What kind of way is that to kill somebody?
一根棒球棒?
A baseball bat?
现在我知道你为什么认为谋杀是全民消遣了。
Now I know why you think murder's the national pastime.
棒球棒比枪便宜多了。
Baseball bat is much cheaper than gun.
亚伯拉罕·林肯比乔治·华盛顿还便宜?
Abraham Lincoln is cheaper than George Washington?
我不认识他。
I don't know him.
罗莎莉，你在哪?
Rosalie, where are you?
现在我们要做什么?
Now what are we going to do?
这一次，一切都由我负责。
This time, I take care of everything.
我们明天谈。
We'll talk tomorrow.
这是错误的。这是错误的。
This is wrong. It's wrong.
交给我吧。我自己做。
You leave it to me. I do it myself.
不!不做任何事。
No! Don't do anything.
我们明天谈。
We'll talk tomorrow.
你在这里做什么?
What are you doing out here?
什么?
What?
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
只是透透气。
Just getting some air.
来吧。
Come on.
有个疯子在附近游荡。
There's a maniac loose in the neighborhood.
进屋去。
Get in the house.
什么
What
狗娘养的!
Son of a bitch!
好吧，亚伯拉罕·林肯先生，狗娘养的，混蛋!
All right, Mr. Abraham Lincoln, son of a bitch, bastard!
现在你打算怎么做?
Now what are you going to do, huh?
是的——你在干什么?
Yeah-- What are you doing?
没什么。我有枪。
Nothing. I've got my gun.
你要枪干什么?
What do you want a gun for?
我想那个戴面具的人是想抢劫我。
I figure that guy in the mask is trying to rob me.
生意很好。
Business is good.
人们以为我随身带着很多现金。
People think I carry a lot of cash around.
我不喜欢家里有枪和孩子们在一起。
I don't like having a gun in the house with the children.
*不要忘记你是我的爱人*
* Don't forget You are my darling *
别忘了…＊
* Don't forget to be... *
罗莎莉，来吧，如果你要来的话。
Rosalie, come on, if you're coming.
乔伊,等等。
Joey, wait up.
我不是田径明星。
I'm not a track star.
有什么事吗?
What's the matter?
看看他对这片灌木做了什么。
Look what he did to this bush.
来吧。我们走吧。
Come on. Let's go.
不!不,停止!
No! No, stop!
等等!等待。不,等等。
Wait! Wait. No, wait.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
去工作。
Going to work.
不,等等。
No, wait.
你怎么了?
What's the matter with you?
你们从来不一起上班。
You never go to work together.
所以今天，我们一起走。
So today, we go together.
我不喜欢今天早上我的车发出的声音，你能看看吗?
I didn't like the way my car sounded this morning, so would you look at it?
在星期三下雨的时候，男人和女人一起坐车是很不吉利的。
It's very bad luck for man and woman to go together in car on Wednesday, when it's raining.
下雨了。那又怎样?
It's raining. So what?
它是湿的。
It's wet.
雨总是湿的。
Rain is always wet.
街道是湿的。
The streets are wet.
娜佳妈妈，你在干什么?
Mama Nadja, what are you doing?
你怎么了?
What's the matter with you?
你到底是怎么了?
What the hell's wrong with you?
今天是星期三。
It's Wednesday.
你介意吗?我们得去工作了。
Do you mind? We've got to go to work.
星期三的交通很糟糕，尤其是街上潮湿的时候。
Traffic is bad on Wednesdays, especially when streets are wet.
你想让我因为堵车而待在家里?
You want me to stay home because of traffic?
我想让罗莎莉待在家里帮我打扫房间。
I want Rosalie to stay home and help me with the housecleaning.
清扫房间吗?
Housecleaning?
我有工作要做。
I've got work to do.
不!
No!
你们俩怎么了?
What's the matter with you two?
你为什么不告诉我你要炸了那辆车?
Why didn't you tell me you were going to blow up the car?
我想这对你来说会是个惊喜。
I thought it would be a nice surprise for you.
妈妈，我们说的不是生日派对。
Mama, we're not talking about a birthday party.
我们要杀的是他，不是我。
We're supposed to be killing him, not me.
我不知道哪里出了问题。
I don't know what goes wrong.
我把电线从分电器盖连接到油箱里的火花塞。
I run a wire from distributor cap to spark plug in gas tank.
我想当他发动汽车时，砰!
I figure when he starts car, boom!
整个东西都在上升。
Whole thing goes up.
再见,乔伊。
Bye-bye, Joey.
乔伊不应该那样死。
Joey shouldn't die that way.
那是一种可怕的死法。
That's a terrible way to die.
他应该怎么死呢?
Well, how should he die?
我不知道，但更…更好的吗?
I don't know, but something a little more... Nicer?
我会考虑的。
I'll think about it.
他仍然是我的丈夫。
He's still my husband.
你自己也说过你恨他。
You said yourself you hate him.
当我想到他跟那么多女人在一起时——哦，天哪，妈妈!
When I think of all the women he's been with-- Oh, God, Mama!
他欺骗你，愚弄你。
He cheats on you and makes a fool of you.
我知道。我知道。
I know. I know.
罗莎莉，求你了，如果你不杀他，就杀了你自己。
Rosalie, please, if you don't kill him, kill yourself.
我相信可以安排。
I'm sure that can be arranged.
我看到代码特别声明——站在队列中!
I see the code specifically states-- Stand fast in the ranks!
你跟我说的是密码?
You speak to me of code?
什么代码?
What code?
懦夫的代码。
A coward's code.
你对士兵守则了解多少?
What do you know of the Soldier's Code?
很多胡椒。
A lot of pepper.
一些不错的牛至。
Some nice oregano.
再加一点罗勒。
And a little basil.
很多安眠药。
A lot of sleeping pills.
你确定他不会进来吗?
You sure he won't come in here?
乔伊?不是一个机会。
Joey? Not a chance.
他希望得到周到的服务。
He expects to be waited on hand and foot.
妈妈，别尝。
Mama, don't taste it.
需要更多的辣椒。
Needs more pepper.
让它辣。
Make it spicy.
一点盐。
A little salt.
还有一点酒。
And a splash of wine.
还有很多安眠药。
And a lot of sleeping pills.
到目前为止你投了多少钱?
How much did you put in so far?
整整两瓶。
Two whole bottles.
什么?
What?
应该足以杀人了。
Should be enough to kill anyone.
即使是乔伊。
Even Joey.
他要做这件事。
He's going to do it.
相信我，他真的会这么做的。
Believe me, he's really going to do it.
给你。
Here you go.
我警告你，斋藤上校。
I warn you, Colonel Saito.
孩子们在哪里?
Where are the kids?
他们在露西阿姨家过周末。
They're at Aunt Lucy's for the weekend.
一定要让他吃。
Make sure he eats it.
你在看什么?
What are you looking at?
你的意大利面怎么样?
How's your spaghetti?
好的。
Okay.
有很多更多。
There's plenty more.
这是最好吃的意大利面，罗莎莉。
It's the best spaghetti ever, Rosalie.
看，又香又辣，跟我妈做的一样。
See, nice and spicy, just like my mother's.
没关系。
That's okay.
真可惜孩子们都在露西阿姨家。
Too bad the kids are at Aunt Lucy's.
他们错过了一顿大餐。
They're missing a great meal.
一个帮助。
One more helping.
再给我拿一瓶啤酒来。
And bring me another beer.
怎么了?你不是饿了吗?
What's the matter? You're not hungry?
我感觉不太好。
I don't feel so good.
没有?
No?
有点胃痛。
A little stomachache.
这是所有吗?
Is that all?
"就这些了"是什么意思
What do you mean, "Is that all?"
你想让我吃什么?
What do you want me to have?
也许你应该吃点东西。
Maybe you should take something.
像什么?
Like what?
再来点意大利面怎么样?
How about some more spaghetti?
意大利面条?
Spaghetti?
解决了肚子。
Settles the stomach.
我去拿点来。
I'll go get some.
我不知道。
I don't know.
也许我给他的不够多。
Maybe I didn't give him enough.
但他吃了整整三碗。
But he had three whole bowls.
一头牛。
What an ox.
乔伊不是正常人。
Well, Joey is not a normal man.
你知道他这个人。
You know how he is.
每天工作14到15个小时，一周工作7天，每晚睡眠从不超过2到3个小时。
Works 14, 15 hours a day, seven days a week, never sleeps more than two or three hours a night.
每晚都和不同的女人约会。
Out with a different woman every night.
罗莎莉……他想吃什么就吃什么，从来没长胖过。
Rosalie... He eats anything he wants, never gains any weight.
他不是人类。
He's not human.
就像某种动物。
It's like some kind of animal.
我们面对的是一台机器。
We're dealing with a machine.
罗莎莉!什么?
Rosalie! What?
我现在感觉好多了。
I feel better now.
我玩得很开心。这就是我所需要的。
I had a good crap. That's all I needed.
多么美丽的夜晚啊!
What a beautiful night!
看到了吗?
See?
意思是不要忘记你是我的宝贝
* Means don't forget You are my darlings *
来吧。你不唱歌。
Come on. You're not singing.
*不要忘记你对我来说意味着一切……＊
* Don't forget to be All you mean to me... *
*我的爱就像一颗星星*我的爱人*闪耀着明亮而清晰的光芒只因为你在这里*
* My love is like a star * My darling * Shining bright and clear Just because you're here *
请不要忘记……你为什么要走?＊
* Please do not forget... * Why the hell Are you leaving? *
来吧,女士们。我们走吧。
Come on, ladies. Let's go.
垄断。
Monopoly.
噢，野兔今晚可爽了。
Whoa, the Wild Hare is feeling his oats tonight.
结束电话。
A close call.
这就是它的样子，但我们要等测量结果出来。
That's what it looks like, but we'll wait for the measurement.
没有更多的。
No more.
你完成它。
You finish it.
起跑线起飞使他占了上风。
A starting-line launch gave him the advantage.
完全悬浮在赛车上方，但在冠军赤脚后面几英寸。
Completely airborne over the cars, but inches behind Barefoot, the winner.
乔伊
Joey
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我们朝他开枪。
We shoot him.
不!不。
No! No.
但我们必须这么做。我们现在不能回去了。
But we have to. We can't go back now.
不，我们做得太过分了。
No, we've gone too far.
如果我们带他去医院，他们会发现他总是做白日梦。
If we take him to the hospital, they find him full of dreamies.
他们会知道我们想杀他。
They'll know we tried to kill him.
我们别无选择。
We have no choice.
我们不能这么做。
We can't do that.
我们不能杀他，妈妈。
We can't shoot him, Mama.
我们可以不?不!
We can't? No!
好的，我们找到德沃了。
Okay, we get Devo.
他的哥哥是海军陆战队的。
His brother was in Marines.
他知道枪。
He knows guns.
你好。
Hello.
Devo,娜迪亚。
Devo, it's Nadja.
嘿,娜迪亚。
Hey, Nadja.
你独自吗?
Are you alone?
是的,为什么?
Yeah, why?
好。
Good.
戴沃，你知道你对罗莎莉的感觉吗?
Devo, you know how you feel about Rosalie?
你怎么说你有多喜欢她?
How you say how much you like her?
我爱罗莎莉。
I love Rosalie.
你愿意为她做什么?
And how you would do anything for her?
是的,任何东西。绝对的。
Yes, anything. Absolutely.
什么吗?是的,任何东西。为什么?
Anything? Yeah, anything. Why?
你是个好孩子，很贴心。
You are a good boy, very sweet.
我想让你帮我和罗莎莉一个小忙。
I want you to do a little favor for Rosalie and me.
你来我家，我告诉你这是什么。
You come to the house, I'll tell you what it is.
好的。
Okay.
稍等。等一下。
Wait a moment. Wait a minute.
床单很珍贵。
The bedspread is very precious.
别毁了它。
Don't ruin it.
好的。在他的背上。
Okay. On his back.
你知道该怎么做。
You know what to do.
等待。你要去哪里?
Wait. Where are you going?
我不能看。
I can't watch.
我一个人做不到。
I can't do this alone.
他是我的丈夫。
He's my husband.
你到底想不想让他死?
Do you want him dead or not?
我要他死，但我不希望他受伤。
I want him dead, but I don't want him hurt.
他不会受伤的。他不会。
He won't get hurt. He won't.
他的声音睡着了。
He's sound asleep.
是的。
Yeah.
我们要让他永远沉睡下去。
We're keeping him asleep forever.
我不能看。
I can't watch.
罗莎莉!
Rosalie!
多久没见了?
How long has it been?
很快，乔伊醒了。然后呢?
Pretty soon, Joey wakes up. Then what?
我做不到。我要阻止他。
I can't do it. I'm going to stop him.
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
我没事吧?
Am I all right?
我是不是你为什么要问我是否还好?
Am I all-- Why are you asking me if I'm all right?
他才是那个中枪的人。
He's the one who got shot.
你最好坐下。
You'd better sit down.
不!我不想坐下。
No! I don't want to sit down.
乔伊呢?
What about Joey?
他是活着还是死了?
Is he alive or dead?
我不知道。
I don't know.
血。
Blood.
不,番茄酱。
No, tomato sauce.
番茄酱吗?
Tomato sauce?
你到底有没有朝他开枪?
Did you shoot him or not?
我想是的。
I think so.
你是什么意思?我听到一声枪响。
What do you mean? I heard a shot.
我朝他开了一枪，但我不知道有没有打中他。
I shot him, but I don't know if I hit him.
我是说，我在最后一秒把头扭开了。
I mean, I turned my head away at the last second.
抱歉，但我实在看不下去了。
I'm sorry, but I couldn't bear to watch.
我以为你懂枪。
I thought you knew about guns.
我以前从没开过枪。
I never shot anyone before.
哦,别担心。我明白了。
Oh, don't worry. I understand.
凡事都有第一次。
There's a first time for everything.
我读到过一个牙科保健师妈妈，没关系。
I read about a dental hygienist-- Mama, never mind.
哦,等等。有一些血。
Oh, wait. There's some blood.
让我看看。
Let me see.
它是什么?
What is it?
我觉得是个弹孔。这是非常小的。
I think it's a bullet hole. It's very small.
一颗子弹洞吗?你确定吗?
A bullet hole? Are you sure?
是的,我肯定。
Yes, I'm sure.
他死了吗?
Is he dead?
乔伊乔伊?
Joey Joey?
罗莎莉。什么?
Rosalie. What?
我觉得不太热。有点头疼。
I don't feel so hot. Got a little headache.
我的胃也不觉得那么热了。
My stomach don't feel so hot neither.
你被病毒感染了，亲爱的
You got a virus, honey.
就是这样一种病毒
That's all, a virus.
病毒洛维医生来过
Virus Dr. Lowe was here.
他是吗?
He was?
是的。
Yeah.
我不记得了。
I don't remember.
对，他来过，给了你机会。
Yeah, he was here, and he gave you a shot.
哦……
Ohh...
能给我一杯水吗?
Can I get a glass of water?
罗莎莉吗?
Rosalie?
也许我也吃两片阿司匹林。
Maybe I take a couple of aspirin too.
哦,好的。
Oh, okay.
哇。
Whoa.
我们该怎么办?
What are we going to do?
你得再朝他开一枪。
You're going to have to shoot him again.
不。我不能。
No. I can't.
我不敢相信我第一次就做到了。
I can't believe I did it the first time.
真不敢相信你让我这么做。
I can't believe you let me do that.
如果你做不到，你就得找一个能做到的人。
If you can't do it, you have to find someone who can.
我来出钱。
I'll put up the money.
我们需要专业人士。
We need professionals.
这件事必须马上做。
This has to be done right away.
哦，你认识什么人?
Oh, you know someone?
我需要振作起来。
I need to collect myself.
好了，控制住。
All right, get a grip.
振作起来。好吧?好的。我们走吧。
Get your shit together. Okay? Okay. Let's go.
我们能付多少钱?
How much can we pay?
尽我们所能。
As much as we have to.
是啊，不过也不是太多。
Yeah, not too much, though.
你知道，尽量打折。
You know, try for discount.
这里有哈兰·詹姆斯吗?
Is there a Harlan James here?
后面的，德沃。
In the back, Devo.
哈兰，最近怎么样?
Hello, Harlan, how's it going?
Devo。
Devo.
你说呢?
What do you say?
你认识我表哥马龙吗?
You know my cousin Marlon?
我当然知道。你好吗，马龙?
Well, of course I do. How are you, Marlon?
什么?
What?
300美元不算多。
$300 is not much.
他已经死亡。
He's already dying.
你要做的就是干掉他。
All you have to do is finish him off.
它仍然是——
It's still--
它仍然是谋杀!
It's still murder!
但我已经完成了大部分工作。
But I've already done most of the work.
我告诉你，600块就能搞定。
I'll tell you, we'll do it for $600.
400美元。
$400.
他都快快入土了。
He's practically got one foot in the grave.
550美元。你说呢?
$550. What do you say?
如果我们要浪费这家伙，我们应该得到报酬，伙计。
If we're going to waste the dude, we ought to get paid for it, man.
这是美国人的方式，对吗?
That's the American way, right?
是的。
Yeah.
是啊，我是说，我们不是…这里有共产主义者，你知道吗?
Yeah, I mean, we're not... communists here, you know?
我们是美国人。我们有谋生的权利。
We're Americans. We got a right to make a living.
500美元。这是我的最终报价。
$500. That's my final offer.
你告诉他。
You tell him.
好的。
Okay.
你感觉怎么样，乔伊?
How you feeling, Joey?
有点累了。
A little tired.
你真的病了，宝贝。
You're real sick, baby.
是的。
Yeah.
也许我睡着了，嘿?
Maybe I sleep, hey?
我在哪里?
What Where am I?
你被病毒感染了，亲爱的没关系。
You got a virus, honey. It's okay.
一个病毒。
A virus.
哦,是的。我忘记了。
Oh, yes. I forgot.
你能看到什么吗?
Can you see anything?
不。
No.
等一下。这是什么东西。
Wait a minute. Here is something.
这是一辆出租车。不可能是为了我们。
It's a cab. It can't be for us.
你想吃一口吗?
Do you want a bite?
不。
No.
这些人是谁?
Who are these guys?
8.50美元,请。
$8.50, please.
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
计。给我8.50美元。
The meter. Give me $8.50.
他们在做什么?
What are they doing?
我不知道。
I don't know.
他们要去别的地方。
They're going someplace else.
伙计们!在这里。
Guys! Over here.
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
它是在这里。
It's over here.
罗莎莉!
Rosalie!
是我。
It's me.
你打的。
You took a taxi.
你怎么能那样做?
How could you do that?
这有什么问题吗?
What's wrong with that?
你是来杀乔伊的。
You came here to kill Joey.
那又怎样?
So what?
所以乘出租车去犯罪现场通常不被认为是一个好主意。
So it's generally not considered a very good idea to take a taxi to the scene of a crime.
嘿,伙计,看。很酷,对吧?
Hey, man, look. Be cool, okay?
我是说，你知道，那家伙只是个出租车司机。
I mean, you know, the dude's only a taxi driver.
他不像他叫什么名字。
He's not like what's his name.
他叫什么名字?
What's his name?
谁?
Who?
你知道的。
You know.
是的,对的。
Yeah, right.
看,没关系。
Look, never mind.
算了吧。这是完成了。好吗?
Forget it. It's done. Okay?
这是罗莎莉，乔伊的妻子，这是罗莎莉的母亲。
This is Rosalie, Joey's wife, and this is Rosalie's mother.
哈伦,马龙。
Harlan, Marlon.
小心
Be careful.
很高兴认识你。
Nice to meet you.
最近怎么样?
How's it going?
你想喝点咖啡或茶或吃点什么吗?在你开始之前?
Would you like some coffee or tea or something to eat before you... Well, before you get started?
不。谢谢。
No. Thanks.
我们很酷。
We're cool.
打扰一下，哈兰，马龙。
Excuse me, Harlan, Marlon.
就一会儿，我想跟戴沃说几句话。
Just for one second, I'd like to have a word with Devo over here.
他们看起来像瘾君子。
They look like drug addicts.
他们都是瘾君子。
Well, they are drug addicts.
哦,我的上帝!你雇了瘾君子?
Oh, my God! You hired drug addicts?
你想让我雇谁，红十字会吗?
Who did you expect me to hire, the Red Cross?
他们看起来很有礼貌。
They seem like very polite boys.
我不喜欢吸毒者来我家。
I don't like drug addicts in my house.
罗莎莉，拜托，别把他们当成瘾君子。
Rosalie, please, don't think of them as drug addicts.
把他们想象成杀手。
Think of them as killers.
袋鼠是怎么生下人类宝宝的?
How can a kangaroo give birth to a human baby?
这是一个奇迹。这里写着呢。
It's a miracle. It says so right here.
是合法的吗?
Is that legal?
你知道的…和袋鼠做爱?
You know... having sex with a kangaroo?
在这儿。
Here it is.
哦,对不起。
Oh, sorry.
口径的。
.22 caliber.
不是什么好枪。
Not much of a gun.
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
是有点小，你知道吗?
Well, it's kind of small, you know?
不太流行。
Not much pop.
好吧，这就是我们所知道的。
Well, that's all we've got.
是的，这是我们的枪。
Yeah, this is our gun.
放点音乐，好吗?
Put on some music, okay?
声音要大，这样就能盖过枪声了。
Make it real loud so's it drowns out the noise of the gunshot.
是的,哦。
Yeah, ooh.
在后面，右边。
In the back, on the right.
在角落里。看到灯了吗?门。
In the corner. See the lamp? Door.
那是干什么用的?
What is that for?
我不知道。
I don't know.
以防万一，万一他醒了。
Just in case, you know, like if he wakes up.
哦,好的。
Oh, okay.
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
是的,我想。
Yeah, I guess.
你呢，乔伊?你准备好了吗?
How about you, Joey? You ready?
让我们做它。
Let's do it.
哈伦吗?
Harlan?
什么?
What?
我以前从没杀过人。
I never killed nobody before.
他已经半死不活的境地。
He's already half-dead.
即便如此，我的意思是…你知道，我也没杀过人。
Even so, I mean... you know-- I never killed nobody neither.
那又怎样?能有多难?
So what? How hard can it be?
我是说，我们所做的就是…我们宣读他的权利，然后杀了他。
I mean, all's we do is... we read him his rights and then kill him.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
寻找记录。
Looking for a record.
妈妈，任何唱片都可以。
Mama, any record will do.
我在找约翰尼·马西斯。
I'm looking for Johnny Mathis.
我爱他。
I love him.
玩这一套。
Play this one.
什么不，罗莎莉，求你了。
What No, Rosalie, please.
你知道我喜欢约翰尼·马西斯。
You know I love Johnny Mathis.
该死的音乐在哪里?
Where's the fucking music?
我不知道。
I don't know.
我不想整晚都坐在这里。
I don't want to sit here all night.
罗莎莉吗?
Rosalie?
看看这个。
Look at that.
什么?
What?
那是雷吉·杰克逊的模型。
That's a Reggie Jackson model.
噢,是的。
Oh yeah.
雷吉!
Reggie!
雷吉!雷吉!雷吉!
Reggie! Reggie! Reggie!
我爱雷吉。
I love Reggie.
我也是,男人。他是最伟大的。
Me too, man. He's the greatest.
他打了多少本垒打?
How many homers has he hit?
我的意思是,一生。
I mean, lifetime.
他妈的,人。
Shit, man.
哇。
Wow.
他妈的。
Fuck.
一群。
A bunch.
雷吉!雷吉!雷吉!雷吉!雷吉!
Reggie! Reggie! Reggie! Reggie! Reggie!
他们想听雷鬼音乐。
They want to hear reggae music.
雷鬼音乐吗?是的。
Reggae? Yes.
不，就在这里的某个地方。我知道是这样。
No, it's right here somewhere. I know it is.
我在外面等你。
I'll be waiting outside.
为什么?
Why?
因为我再也受不了了。
Because I can't stand this anymore.
什么是雷鬼音乐?
What is reggae music?
我要杀了这家伙。
I'm going to shoot this dude.
我等得不耐烦了。
I'm sick of waiting.
你要在哪里射杀他?
Where you going to shoot him?
在这里。
Right here.
你觉得呢，我要带他去市中心吗?
What do you think, I'm going to take him downtown?
不。我是说，他身上什么地方?
No. I mean, where on his body?
嗯，我不知道。我猜是他的心脏。
Well, I don't know. His heart, I guess.
这是哪一边的?他的心吗?
Which side is that on? His heart?
哦,狗屎,人。我不知道。
Oh, shit, man. I don't know.
它就在那里的某个地方。
It's in there somewhere.
我什么都没听到。
I don't hear nothing.
等一下。
Wait a minute.
学校。
School.
什么?
What?
学校，伙计，你知道的。忠诚的承诺。
School, man, you know. Pledge allegiance.
哦,是的。
Oh, yeah.
交出你的心脏。
Hand over your heart.
是的,对的。
Yeah, right.
我宣誓效忠美利坚合众国国旗。
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America.
敬共和国…在一个无形的国家…上帝庇佑下的国家…宽阔的天空和自由的琥珀坟墓……救我们脱离自由。
And to the republic... under one invisible nation... Nations under God whose... Spacious skies and amber graves of liberty for all... Deliver us from freedom.
哈伦。什么?
Harlan. What?
我看不下去了，伙计。
I can't watch this, man.
猫咪。
Pussy.
这一边。这一边。
This side. This side.
啊!他妈的!
Aah! Fuck!
你应该在开拍前戴上的!
You were supposed to put it on before the shot!
是的，他们射得太快了。
Yeah, they shoots too fast.
好吗?
Well?
好吧,什么?
Well, what?
他死了吗?
Is he dead?
他当然死了，伙计。
Of course he's dead, man.
你觉得呢?
What do you think?
我拍他。
I shot him.
怎么了?发生了什么事?
What's the matter? What happened?
她心烦意乱。
She's upset.
她会没事的。
She'll be all right.
我以为她想让他死。
I thought she wanted him dead.
我们做了什么，伙计?
What did we do, man?
我们杀错人了吗?
Did we kill the wrong person?
不,不。
No, no.
不，她会没事的。
No, she'll be all right.
我们现在让她一个人呆着。
We leave her alone now.
我很震惊，你知道的。
It's the shock, you know.
音乐。
The music.
我想喝一杯。
I could use a drink.
是的。
Yeah.
是的,好的。是的。哦。
Yeah, okay. Yeah. Ooh.
好主意。
Good idea.
来了。
Come.
我们该为什么干杯?
What should we drink to?
这是乔伊。
Here's to Joey.
那很酷。
That's cool.
这是错误的。
It's wrong.
哦,亲爱的上帝。
Oh, dear Lord.
上帝啊，救救我吧。
Oh, please help me, God.
我真不该这么做。
Oh, I never should have done this thing.
我不该犯这样的罪。哦……不管你对我做什么，上帝，请把乔伊带回来。
I never should have sinned this way. Ohh... I never-- Whatever you do to me, God, please bring Joey back.
罗莎莉吗?
Rosalie?
啊!
Aah!
什么
What
哦!哦!哦!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
什么…哦!
What...oh!
什么……你在这里做什么?
What...what are you doing here?
我在祈祷。
I was praying.
我以为……祈祷吗?
I thought... Praying?
是的。
Yeah.
罗莎莉……我病得没那么严重。
Rosalie...I'm not that sick.
我得到的是什么?
All I got is what?
一个病毒。这是所有。
A little virus. That's all.
乔伊。
Joey.
你怎么还没睡?
What are you doing up?
我听到了鞭炮之类的声音。
I heard a noise like firecracker or something.
把我吵醒了。
Woke me up.
耶稣。
Jesus.
罗莎莉，你怎么不…?
Rosalie, how come you don't...?
你知道的…我们有公司。
You know... we have company.
你没有喂他们。
You're not feeding them.
有什么事吗?
What's the matter?
我们家里没吃的了，还是怎么了?
We got no food in the house, or what?
他们不饿，乔伊。
They're not hungry, Joey.
他们不想吃任何东西。
They don't want anything to eat.
我不知道，我认识所有人吗?
I don't know-- Do I know everybody?
嗯,是的。
Uh, yeah.
嗯…嗯…他是好的吗?
Well...um... Is he okay?
是的。
Yeah.
我是马龙
I'm Marlon--
我是说，我是威廉。
I mean, I'm William.
我是威廉·布朗。
I'm William Brown.
我路易……詹姆斯。不。
I'm Louie... James. No.
不,等等。
No, wait.
路易……史密斯吗?
Louie... Smith?
史密斯。
Smith.
乔伊的披萨。
Joey's Pizza.
一些奶酪和饼干?
Some cheese and crackers?
来点椒盐卷饼吧?
Maybe some pretzels, huh?
你感觉怎么样，乔伊?
How are you feeling, Joey?
你还好吗?
You feeling all right?
谢谢你！
Thank you.
什么?
What?
感觉好吗?
Feeling okay?
嗯…不，我不觉得很热。不。
Uh... No, I don't feel so hot. No.
你好,Devo。
Hello, Devo.
蜂蜜。
Honey.
乔伊……你不应该下床。
Joey...you shouldn't be out of bed.
你感染了严重的病毒
You got a bad virus.
来吧。
Come on.
你告诉我。
You're telling me.
这种病毒会要了我的命
It's killing me, this virus.
好了，大家晚安。
Well, good night, everybody.
哎呦。
Whoops.
乔伊，把裤子穿好。
Joey, pull your pants up.
很高兴认识你。
Nice to meet you.
你确定他们不饿吗?
You sure they're not hungry?
我肯定,宝贝。
I'm positive, baby.
我们可以派人去买中国菜。
We could send out for Chinese.
不，他们什么都不想要。
No, they don't want anything.
我们有意大利面条。
We got spaghetti.
我很失望。
I am very disappointed.
好男人。
Nice guys.
哦,你没事吧?
Ooh, you okay?
什么?
What?
我们还有肉丸吗?
We got any meatballs left?
什么，你饿了吗?
What, are you hungry?
可以吃点东西。
Could eat a little something.
你知道的，让我恢复体力。
You know, get my strength back.
来吧。对不起。
Come on. Sorry.
现在几点了?
What time is it?
这是晚了。
It's late.
你应该试着睡觉。
You should try to sleep.
好好照顾我，罗莎莉。
You take good care of me, Rosalie.
我知道你喜欢。
I know you do.
你是我的丈夫。
You're my husband.
罗莎莉。
Rosalie.
是吗?
Yeah?
哦,乔伊,没有。
Oh, Joey, no.
不,不是现在。来吧。
No, not now. Come on.
静静地躺着，好吗?
Just lie quietly, okay?
这只有200。
This is only 200.
他们答应给我们五个。
We was promised five.
因为杀了他，五。
For killing him, five.
因为伤了他，2分。
For wounding him, two.
你想让我杀了他，对吧?
Well, you wanted me to shoot him, right?
所以我开枪打了他。
So I shot him.
你把他吵醒了。那有什么好处?
You woke him up. What good is that?
好的。
Okay.
下次再这样做，我们会提前拿到钱的。
Next time we do this, we're going to get paid in advance.
如果我们继续朝乔伊开枪，你不觉得他会起疑心吗?
If we keep shooting Joey, don't you think he might get suspicious?
拉里。
Larry.
把你跟我说的告诉他。
Tell him what you told me.
我想做笔交易。
I want to make a deal.
不是那个，是另一件事。
Not that, the other thing.
我的牢房没有足够的热量。
There's not enough heat in my cell.
不，是哈兰和马龙。
No, Harlan and Marlon.
噢,是的。
Oh yeah.
哈兰·詹姆斯和他的表姐马龙。
Harlan James and his cousin Marlon.
我听说他们花了很多钱去袭击乔伊·博卡。
I heard they was paid a lot of money to hit Joey Boca.
乔伊·博卡，我不知道。我是这么听说的，你知道吗?
Joey Boca I don't know. That's what I heard, you know?
哈伦和马龙给每个人买酒，然后炫耀。
Harlan and Marlon was buying drinks for everyone and bragging on it.
说他们杀了那家伙。说他们有五千美元。
Said they shot the dude. Said they got $5,000.
有点晚了。也许他们是睡着了。
It's kind of late. Maybe they're asleep.
我最好的答案。我不得不这么做。
I'd better answer. I have to.
不。不。罗莎莉……听着，不管发生什么，让我来跟你谈。
No. No. Rosalie... Now, look, whatever happens, let me do the talking.
妈妈，我不想让你说什么。
Mama, I don't want you to say anything.
什么?
What?
你太,Devo。
You too, Devo.
没必要每个人都惹上麻烦。
There's no sense everyone getting in trouble.
但我不想你惹上麻烦。
But I don't want you to get in trouble.
总之，乔伊没死，你知道的。
Anyway, Joey's not dead, you know.
我们所做的就是让他睡着，然后叫醒他几次。
All we did was put him to sleep and wake him up a few times.
妈妈，他中了两枪。
Mama, he has two bullets in him.
他可能要死了。
He could be dying.
那他为什么想吃肉丸呢?
So how come he wants meatballs?
晚上,罗莎莉。
Evening, Rosalie.
是错了吗?
Is something wrong?
我们可以进来吗?
May we come in?
哦，你是说现在?
Oh, you mean now?
我们想见乔伊。
We'd like to see Joey.
乔伊?
Joey?
你的丈夫。乔伊。
Your husband. Joey.
哦,是的,乔伊。哦,乔伊。
Oh, yeah, Joey. Oh, Joey.
他现在不太舒服。
Uh, well, he's not feeling well right now.
你过几天再来吧?
Maybe you could come back in a couple of days?
乔伊非常恶心。
Joey very sick.
你改天再来吧。
You come back some other time.
我们今晚想见见他。
We'd like to see him tonight.
可能明天吧。
Maybe tomorrow.
罗莎莉，如果有必要，我们会带着搜查令回来。
Rosalie, if we have to, we'll come back with a warrant.
乔伊?
Joey?
嘿，拉里，你好吗?
Hey, Larry, how you doing?
你对吧?
You all right?
我染上了点病毒
I got a little virus.
一个病毒?
A virus?
是的某种病毒
Yes, some kind of virus.
我头痛。
I got a headache.
你介意我开灯吗?
You mind if I turn on the light?
当然。去做吧。
Sure. Go ahead.
我认为你不应该。
I don't think you should.
就一会儿。
Just for a second.
不管怎样，这是行不通的。
It doesn't work, anyway.
哦。
Oh.
让你舒适舒适。
Get you nice and comfortable.
对不起,罗莎莉。请原谅我。
Excuse me, Rosalie. Excuse me, please.
请原谅我。谢谢你！
Please, excuse me. Thank you.
耶稣。
Jesus.
什么?
What?
这到底是怎么回事?
What the hell's going on here?
他头部中枪了。
He's been shot in the head.
真的吗?什么?
Really? What?
难怪他头疼。
No wonder he has headache.
头痛吗?他身上有颗子弹。
Headache? He's got a bullet in him.
卡洛斯，马上叫辆救护车过来。
Carlos, get an ambulance over here right away.
Devo !
Devo!
我想给乔伊拿个创可贴。
I was going to get a Band-Aid for Joey.
我是卡洛斯·威利警探。
Yeah, this is Detective Carlos Wiley.
我在北C区424号，跟"查理"一样
I'm at 424 North C, as in "Charlie."
不是我们干的。我对天发誓我们没有。
We didn't do it. I swear to God we didn't.
我们在外面的草坪上发现了他。
We found him outside on the lawn.
是的。他躺在那里。
Yeah. He was lying there.
有人朝他开枪，把他扔在草地上。
Someone had shot him and thrown him on the lawn.
真是一团糟。
It was a mess.
太可怕了，所以我们……我们把他带进屋，放在床上。
It was terrible, so we... we brought him inside and we put him in bed.
是的，就像你看到的。
Yeah, like you see.
肯定是黑手党干的。
And it must have been the Mafia.
黑手党吗?
Mafia?
黑手党。
The Mafia.
乔伊是意大利人。
Yeah, Joey was Italian.
他是意大利人。
He is Italian.
罗莎莉，你为什么不送他去医院?
Rosalie, why didn't you take him to the hospital?
他不想去。
He didn't want to go.
他觉得不能胜任。
He wasn't feeling up to it.
乔伊，你不想去医院吗?
Joey, you didn't want to go to the hospital?
不。为什么，因为病毒?
No. Why, for a virus?
罗莎莉。不要告诉罗莎莉。
Rosalie. Don't tell Rosalie.
你给他吃了多少瓶药?
How many bottles of pills did you give him?
我给了他两瓶。一,二。
I gave him two bottles. One, two.
哈伦和马龙说德沃第一次开枪打了他。
Harlan and Marlon say Devo shot him the first time.
是这样吗?
Is that right?
如果不是我，戴沃根本不会在那里。
Devo wouldn't even have been there if it wasn't for me.
你是什么意思?
How do you mean?
我想杀了乔伊。德沃跟这事无关。
I wanted to kill Joey. Devo had nothing to do with it.
德沃到底有没有朝他开枪?
Did Devo shoot him or not?
德沃怎么说?
What does Devo say?
别管他。你说呢?
Never mind him. What do you say?
它不是Devo。这是我。
It wasn't Devo. It was me.
我第一次开枪打了他，然后…谁杀了他?让我看看。这是马龙。
I shot him the first time, and then... Who shot him? Let me see. It was Marlon.
不,不。哈伦。哈伦。
No, no. Harlan. Harlan.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
是的,我肯定。为什么?你觉得是谁杀了他?
Yeah, I'm sure. Why? Who do you think shot him?
你妈妈呢?
What about your mother?
她跟这事一点关系都没有。什么都没有。
She had nothing to do with it. Nothing.
是的，我杀了他。是的。
Yes, I shoot him. Yes.
你知道为什么吗?他是个没用的混蛋。
You know why? He is no-good son of a bitch.
谁给他的药?
Who gave him the pills?
我做到了。你觉得呢?
I did. What do you think?
我先给他安眠药，然后杀了他。
First I give him sleeping pills, then I shoot him.
你想让我认罪?
You want me to confess?
给我一张纸。我承认。
Give me piece of paper. I confess.
罗莎莉呢?
What about Rosalie?
罗莎莉吗?她什么也不做。
Rosalie? She does nothing.
不，我什么都做。
No, I do everything.
我给他吃药，开枪，什么都做。
I give him pills, I shoot him, everything.
你这么做的时候，你女儿在做什么?
And while you were doing this, what was your daughter doing?
她求我停下来。
She was begging me to stop.
但我还是做了，你知道为什么吗?
But I do it anyway, and you know why?
我是她的妈妈。我做我喜欢做的事。
I am her mother. I do what I like.
我以为德沃第一次开枪打了他。
I thought Devo shot him the first time.
Devo吗?
Devo?
哦,不。你一定是在开玩笑。
Oh, no. You must be joking.
不，德沃是个好孩子。
No, Devo's very nice boy.
他不会开枪的。
He wouldn't shoot nobody.
我不明白你为什么要把责任推到罗莎莉身上。
I don't understand why you're trying to blame it on Rosalie.
也许是我干的。
Maybe I did it.
也许我很高兴我这么做了。
Maybe I'm glad I did it.
你是说是你干的?
Are you saying you did it?
不，他没这么说。
No, he's not saying that.
他说了什么?
What's he saying?
他什么也没说。
He's not saying anything.
我知道怎么开枪。
I know how to fire a gun.
我哥哥是国民警卫队的。
My brother was in the National Guard.
你是什么意思?
So what are you saying?
他说他哥哥是个爱国的美国人。
He's saying that his brother is a patriotic American.
博卡女士，这是冲动犯罪吗?
Ms. Boca, was it a crime of passion?
看看这些人。
Look at all these people.
罗莎莉，是我，托尼。你能告诉我什么?
Rosalie, it's me, Tony. What can you tell me?
妈妈，记住，你跟这事无关。
Mama, remember, you had nothing to do with it.
今晚我跟你打赌我们会上电视，你和我。
Tonight I bet you anything we'll be on TV, you and me.
你能想象吗?
Can you imagine?
罗莎莉，你能给我们录一份口供吗?
Rosalie, can you give us a statement?
Devo。德沃，你能告诉我们什么?
Devo. Devo, what can you tell us?
发生了什么事?
What happened?
黑手党真的参与其中吗?
Is it true that the Mafia involved?
我现在没什么可说的。
I have nothing to say at this time.
无可奉告。
No comment.
你呢，先生?
What about you, sir?
离我远点。
Get the fuck away from me.
乔伊呢?他死了吗?
What about Joey? Is he dead, or what?
乔伊是谁?
Who's Joey?
你知道的，那个人。那个家伙。
You know, the guy. The guy.
对，就是那个人。
Oh, yeah, the guy.
他妈的。
Fuck.
他还活着。
He's still alive.
为什么?你知道些什么?
Why? What do you know about it?
哦,没什么。
Oh, nothing.
罗莎莉……
Rosalie...
莱西。
Lacey.
你过得如何?
How you doing?
嗨,乔伊。你感觉如何?
Hi, Joey. How do you feel?
你该看看外面那些记者。
You should see all the reporters outside.
你会很出名的。
You're going to be so famous.
我甚至听说《人物》杂志要采访你。
I even heard People magazine was going to interview you.
蕾西，你现在不该来这里。
Lacey, you shouldn't be here now.
它是不正确的。
It's not right.
但医生说你一周后就能出院了。
But the doctor said you're going to be out in a week.
听着,宝贝…当有人朝你的头开枪…它让你思考。
Listen, baby... when somebody shoot you in the head... it makes you think.
我最近想了很多很多很多我不能再浪费时间了。
I've been doing a lot of thinking lately, a whole lot, and... I can't mess around anymore.
我必须成为，你知道的，一个好丈夫。
I've got to be, you know, a good husband.
从现在开始，我要认真对待我的婚姻。
From now on, I've got to take my marriage a little more serious.
你明白我的意思吗?
You know what I mean?
乔伊，你在说什么?
Joey, what are you saying?
她射杀你。两次。
She shot you. Twice.
不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no, no, no.
她自己根本没朝我开枪。
She never shot me herself, per se.
那我们呢?
So what about us?
这就是我想告诉你的。
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
现在一切都结束了。
That's all over now.
我一直跟你说我爱我妻子。
I always told you I loved my wife.
乔伊，这女人是谁?
Joey, who is this woman?
妈妈，这是蕾西。
Mama, this is Lacey.
她是我的一个朋友。
She's a friend of mine.
我的乔伊得休息了。
My Joey has to get his rest.
你现在不应该在这里。
You shouldn't be here now.
我正要走。
I was just leaving.
很好。刚刚离开。
Good. Just leave.
反正你也不属于这里。
You don't belong here anyway.
你不是他的妻子。
You're not his wife.
待会儿见，乔伊。
I'll see you later, Joey.
你今天感觉怎么样?
How are you feeling today?
好的,妈妈,更好。
Okay, Mama, better.
我今早和罗莎莉谈过了。
I spoke to Rosalie this morning.
你做了吗?她跟你说了什么?
You did? What did she tell you?
她告诉我什么了?
What did she tell me?
她告诉了我真相。
She told me the truth.
你怎么了，你这个大人物?
What's the matter with you, you big shot?
欺骗你的妻子。
Cheating on your wife.
Ai,妈妈!
Ai, Mama!
拜托，我脑袋里有颗子弹。
Please, I got a bullet in my head.
你脑袋里应该有两颗子弹。
You should have two bullets in your head.
三颗子弹!四子弹!
Three bullets! Four bullets!
人工智能!妈妈，求你了，我很抱歉。
Ai! Mama, please, I'm so sorry.
我能说什么呢?
What can I say?
你不告诉我你很抱歉。
You no tell me you're sorry.
不。不。
No. No.
你告诉罗莎莉。
You tell Rosalie.
是啊，好主意。当然,是的。
Oh, si, good idea. Sure, yeah.
否则，我就揍你一顿…好的。
Otherwise, I give you such a beating... Okay.
妈妈，这是个好主意。
Mama, that's a good idea.
哦,不。
Oh, no.
妈妈……
Mama...
人工智能!
Ai!
你怎么能把她保释出来?
How can you bail her out?
你不明白这意味着什么吗?
Don't you see what that means?
这意味着她可以回家了。
It means she can come home.
在医院里，你说你会起诉。
In the hospital, you said you'd prosecute.
我知道,拉里。我改变主意了。
I know, Larry. I changed my mind.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
过去几周我学到了很多。
I learned a lot in the last few weeks.
你心里不会有复仇的念头吧，乔伊?
You wouldn't have revenge on your mind, would you, Joey?
她是我的妻子。
She's my wife.
我想带她回家。
I want to bring her home.
我爱她。
I love her.
你明白吗?
You understand?
她不应该进监狱。
She shouldn't be in prison.
她是我孩子的母亲。
She's the mother of my children.
也许她有很多想杀我的理由。
Maybe she had plenty of good reasons for trying to kill me.
你想过吗?
You ever think of that?
乔，假设她再试一次。
Joe, suppose she tries again.
她可以，你知道的。
She could, you know.
是的,她可以。
Yeah, she could.
你知道罗莎莉。
You know Rosalie.
当她恋爱时，她就是个十足的疯子。
When she's in love, she's a complete maniac.
别为了妈妈把衣服弄湿了。
Don't get your dress wet for Mommy.
我不会的。
I won't.
嘿,Devo !
Hey, Devo!
Devo !
Devo!
你好吗?
How are you?
Devo吗?
Devo?
等待,马龙……看看谁来了。
Wait, Marlon... look who's here.
嘿,哇。
Hey, wow.
你过得如何?
How you doing?
我很好。
I'm okay.
这是谁?
Who is this?
这是乔伊。
This is Joey.
乔伊?
Joey?
你知道的，那个人。
You know, the guy.
那个家伙。
The guy.
哦。哇。乔伊。
Oh. Wow. Joey.
你保释了我们。
You bailed us out.
是的，我保释了所有人。
Yeah, I bail out everybody.
我想重新开始，把往事一笔勾销。
I want to make a new start, wipe the slate clean.
我听说他们可能会指控我们谋杀未遂。
I hear they may charge us with attempted murder.
不,不,不。我不会起诉的。
No, no, no. I'm not going to prosecute.
如果我起诉你，他们也会把罗莎莉关进监狱。
See, if I prosecute you, they're going to put Rosalie in jail too.
我不想那样。
I don't want that.
不，没有我，他们就没有案子。
No, without me, they got no case.
别担心。
Don't worry.
发生的这一切，不是针对你的。
Hey, you know, what happened, it wasn't personal or anything.
是的。
Yeah.
正确的。我的意思是……我们甚至都不认识你。
Right. I mean... we didn't even know you or anything.
是啊，我们不是朋友，就像现在。
Yeah, we weren't friends or anything, like now.
不。不。这样见面不太好。
No. No. It wasn't the best way to meet.
我们最好在他们改变主意之前离开这里。
We'd better get out of here, you know, before they change their mind.
是的。正确的。
Yeah. Right.
这么久,乔伊。
So long, Joey.
我想我们会再见的。
I guess we'll see you around.
好的。
Okay.
哦，多好的人啊。
Oh, what a nice guy.
是的。
Yeah.
罗莎莉是谁?
Who's Rosalie?
乔伊，我对发生的事非常非常抱歉。
Joey, I'm really, really sorry about what happened.
你很久以前就想告诉我了，德沃。
You tried to tell me a long time ago, Devo.
我应该听你的。
I should have listened to you.
我没有好好对待罗莎莉。
I wasn't treating Rosalie right.
罗莎莉是个很棒的女人。
Rosalie is a wonderful lady.
我知道。我要补偿她。
I know. I'm going to make it up to her.
好。
Good.
谢谢你救我出来。
Thanks for bailing me out.
当然,当然。
Sure, sure.
别再朝我脑袋开枪了，好吗?
Just no more shooting me in the head, okay?
为什么不呢?这似乎有所帮助。
Why not? It seems to have helped.
这是事实。
It's the truth.
我头上挨了一枪，感觉好极了。
I got a bullet in my head, I never felt better.
嗨,妈妈。
Hi, Mom.
哦,我的孩子!
Oh, my babies!
哦,多米尼克,多米尼克。
Oh, Dominic, Dominic.
别担心，我们很安全。
Don't worry, we're safe.
别担心。
Don't worry.
那么，你想要什么?
So, what do you want?
我很抱歉对你女儿这么不好。
I'm sorry I treat your daughter so bad.
我打破了我的结婚誓言……但我再也不会破坏任何东西了，我发誓。
I broke my marriage vows... but I don't break nothing ever again, I swear.
这糖果是给我的吗?
And this is for me, this candy?
好吧,我……是的,谢谢你。
Well, I... Yeah, thank you.
你真是个好孩子。
You're very good boy.
是啊，我曾经喜欢过你。
Yeah, you know, I liked you once.
也许我又喜欢上你了…只是巧克力不是我的最爱。
Maybe I like you again... except chocolate is not my favorite.
我喜欢硬糖。
I like hard candy.
好吧，我会记得的不不不。我暂时留着这个。
Well, I'll remember-- No, no, no, no. I keep this for now.
太好了。我等不及要回家了。
Great. I can't wait to get home.
多米尼克。多米尼克,来了。
Dominic. Dominic, come.
你跟我来。
You come with me.
跟我来，我给你一些我的糖果。
Come with me, I give you some of my candy.
我们去找德沃。来了。
We go find Devo. Come.
这是什么?
What's this?
你送我花干什么?
What are you giving me flowers for?
我想让你再嫁给我一次。
I want you to marry me again.
什么?
What?
新的婚姻，新的生活。
A new marriage, new life.
我们有一个盛大的仪式。
We have big ceremony.
你觉得我会犯同样的错误吗?
You think I'm going to make the same mistake?
我们还没离婚呢。
We're not even divorced yet.
你怎么能再娶我?
How can you marry me again?
罗西!罗西!
Rosie! Rosie!
请过来一下。
Come here, please.
我爱你。我保释了你。
I love you. I bailed you out.
别再这样对我了，乔伊。
Don't do this to me again, Joey.
我想杀了你。
I tried to kill you.
不。你救了我的命。
No. You saved my life.
什么?
What?
你给我的那些安眠药，减缓了我的出血速度。
Those sleeping pills you gave me, they slowed down my bleeding.
这是我活着的动力。
It's what kept me alive.
医生告诉我的。
The doctor told me.
狗娘养的，这么多年你一直在骗我。
Son of bitch, you cheated on me all these years.
我现在凭什么相信你?
Why should I trust you now?
因为我改变了。我焕然一新了。
Because I'm changed. I'm a new man.
为什么?为什么突然就来了?
Why? Why now all of a sudden?
因为你开枪打了我。
Because you shot me.
什么?
What?
罗西，当我在医院醒来发现发生了什么，我对自己说，天啊，这个女人，她爱死我了
Oh, Rosie, when I woke up in that hospital and I found out what happened, I said to myself, "My God, this woman, she loves me to death."
她太爱我了，她宁愿杀了我也不愿看到我和别的女人在一起。
She loves me so much she'd rather kill me than see me with another woman.
她已经准备好为我进监狱了，她太爱我了。
She's ready to go to prison for me, she loves me so much.
哦,宝贝。
Oh, baby.
这就是我所需要的，只是感受你的热情，知道你仍然像男人一样爱我……不像个丈夫，像个男人。
That's all I needed, just to feel your passion, to know you still love me like a man... not like a husband, like a man.
你是我的丈夫。
You are my husband.
你应该为此感到骄傲。
You should be proud of it.
我是你的妻子。我一直为此感到骄傲。
I'm your wife. I was always proud of it.
好吧,你是对的。
Okay, you're right.
我是你的丈夫。
I am your husband.
我也会感到骄傲的。
I'll be proud too.
我再也不会欺骗你了。从来没有。
I'll never cheat on you again. Never.
罗西，我爱你。
Oh, Rosie, I love you.
做我的妻子吧。
Be my wife again.
哦,你疯了。
Oh, you're crazy.
你没有看见吗?
Don't you see?
这是我们的命运。
It's our destiny.
我们注定要在一起。
We're doomed to be together.
就像罗密欧与朱丽叶。
Like Romeo and Juliet.
我会永远对你忠诚。
And I'll always be faithful to you.
就像罗密欧与朱丽叶。
Like Romeo and Juliet.
无论什么。
Whatever.
你觉得乔伊能对她忠诚吗?
You think Joey can be faithful to her?
一切皆有可能。
Anything is possible.
他给了我一盒糖果。
He gave me a box of candy.
如果他不是呢?
What if he isn't?
我们再朝他开枪。
We shoot him again.
开玩笑的
Just kidding.